m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10
l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skills [Lightweight Blade]
Skills [Sharp Blade]
Skills [Lightning-Cloaked]
#12 "A Battle I Can't Lose"
200 Years Ago
[Lightning-Cloaked]
Luna Heela
Temperature +5
Emma Brightness
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10
l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia
[Sluggish]
Movements and reactions become slower
m 0 0 b 0 -2 7 -2 10 -2 b 30 -2 50 -2 70 0 b 70 0 70 1 70 1 b 50 2 30 2 10 2 b 7 2 0 2 0 0
Stone Bullet
Create and fire a stone
from around 10~100 centimeters
by using LP.
After that, the stone comes back to you.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10
l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skills [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow] [LP Conversion] [Great Sage] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye]
Skills [Headache Immunity]  [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]  [Improved Back Step]  [Shoulder Rub]
Skills [Lucky Lecher]  [Dungeon Elevator]  [Dragonslayer]  [Holy Flame]  [Water Drop]
Skills [Lightning Strike]  [Magical Fusion]  [Discerning Eye for Items]  [Dancing]  [Sacrifice]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10
l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia
Skills [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [Sacrifice]
Sacrifice
Noir Stardia
Free her without killing her and a path will appear
Illustration: Takehana Note